see uh prominent most that you guys can
build on on defense next year?
>> Well, I think um
you know, we've always wanted to be a
relentless defense, something where the
effort flies off the tape and you see
guys swarming the ball. Um [snorts]
so I think those are things when I
watched the tape yesterday is you see
everyone in the picture, everyone after
first contact trying to get in the mix,
make sure the ball carry gets down. They
[clears throat] got the one run on us.
That was a big run and and you can't
excuse that because we got to get them
on the ground. We had opportunities to
do it. Could have knocked it down. We
didn't. They scored a touchdown. But you
look at the the mixture of runs after
that and they're tough. They scheme your
runs up. They give you a lot of
different looks. Ton of different
personnel groupings. I thought our
defense did a great job getting that run
game settled down and minimized to where
in the second half, you know, you got to
make them throw the football and and we
were able to get the ball off of them
that way. So just overall really
impressed with the growth of our defense
and how these guys have responded. They
understand the scheme. The communication
has been really good. Um and again, you
know, taking the ball off people, you
know, so there's that confidence, the
scoring there as well. And so it's been
fun to watch.
>> Seemed like the defensive line had a
pretty good game yesterday in terms of
containing the run between the tackles.
>> They're doing a great job playing with
their hands. um understanding the
techniques we're asking them to play and
and so again, you're just seeing guys
grow, a ton of guys grow. Getting Shamar
back was fun to watch yesterday. Um I
thought Cedric played a good game
yesterday. Miles continues just to just
have a really good season right now with
where he's at. And so again, it's just
and there's guys I'm not even naming,
you know, I thought everybody played
really well yesterday. So, um just fun
group to watch them continue to grow and
ascend. And that's all we're asking for
them right now. just get better every
single week and minimize your mistakes.
And we're seeing that from those guys. I
>> think after the game, T. Higgins said he
saw specialists uh to go what when what
did he go see?
>> Thursday morning.
>> Okay. And kind of what what led to y'all
come to that conclusion of saying, "Hey,
let's go have this checked out and kind
of walk us through that process."
>> Yeah, that was the doctors, you know, I
think just making sure uh te in
conjunction with our doctors just making
sure you [clears throat] got that um
final checkpoint there to to make sure
we were seeing everything and the
clearance was appropriate. I think with
the two issues he's had, you know, that
was the appropriate way to do it. And
so, um, get him out there quite early.
It was a it was a bang bang Thursday
morning. Got out there, got back before
pra I wasn't expecting him at practice
and there he is walks in the door, you
know, right after stretch. So, um, that
was I think it was good for him to to
hear that, too. You he can probably
answer that better than I can, but um,
we just want to make sure we were doing
right by him. If he's going to go out
there and play that everybody feels good
about it, he feels good about it. Family
feels good about it. and and he went out
there and to my eye felt really good.
>> What hurdles did you need to clear
Saturday and Sunday morning in order to
to finally have the green light to be
able to play Sunday?
>> I I don't know what the final hurdle
was. I mean, I felt good Friday. I
wasn't going to tell everybody that, but
um you know, it's it's kind of nice for
you to have T. Higgins walk on the field
Sunday morning when no one's exactly
sure if he's going to play. I knew he
was going to play at that point, but um
you know, so it's good to get T back out
there and I know we got a lot of
confidence when he's out there.
>> Jaylen Davis in November. Cam Taylor
gets hurt. You were going young at a lot
of different positions. You had young
corners and obviously it's worked out
with Jaylen. What made Jaylen the guy
that you wanted to put in the lineup
when you looked at your options at that
point?
>> He's always he's always been a
dependable guy. We've seen it for him
and training camp and preseason games
and opportunity he's gotten over the
years, you know, to play in a real game
and
uh you know, just tremendous locker room
guy. I think he's he's a fan favorite in
the locker room. uh tremendous energy,
just does what it takes to win and help
our team. Whether that's been as a
practice squad player, bringing energy
every single day and being consistent
and being ready when his number's called
and so then his number's finally called
in November, he just goes out there and
just plays with a ton of confidence, ton
of awareness, great communication
skills, uh leadership on defense,
um has a knack for making plays on the
ball, has a knack for pressuring. a lot
of similarities Mike Hilton, you know,
and and whether that's because they were
together for a long time and uh and
that's a huge compliment, you know,
because Mike obviously has tremendous
career and so JD's out there doing his
own thing and and really just happy to
see him take on that role and do with a
ton of confidence and make a lot of
plays for us and have a lot of success.
He's earned that.
>> How would you describe Fairchild's
rookie year?
>> Good. you know, I think he's playing
between Orlando and Ted has been really
good for him. Um, played with really
good physicality and, you know, seen a
lot of stuff over the course of the
season being able to be available and
and I, you know, really I think he's got
a really high ceiling and and, you know,
felt the line as a whole, you know,
we're talking about Amar, I guess, we're
talking about Dylan, I just had a ton of
confidence all year, you know, whatever
we're calling that there's going to be
great protection for our quarterbacks.
um that the run game, you know, we're
going to have success in our runs that
we're calling and so just, you know,
that speaks to Dylan, that speaks to the
whole group. Um I just as as a head
coach, as a play caller, have a lot of
confidence in that unit.
>> How much did you like watching tape that
duo blocked Ted and Dylan had for
touchdown?
Well, it's great and it's, you know,
when you get a drive, uh, mullet over
drives in the second half started around
midfield, which was, which was which is
great, but, you know, you hit them in
the pass game and you kind of got teams
on their heels and then you get to hit
them on two runs as you get lower in
there and scored on two runs, you know,
from, you know, inside the 15, inside
the five. Um, it's good because now, you
know, you're having a lot of success in
the pass game. So, they got to respect
that. Then, you know, you hit them with
with some of the runs we hit them on and
and the guys are able to come off the
ball and drive them off the ball and
it's it's that's a great way to finish
drives.
>> Zach, when it's a season that hasn't
gone well for you guys, there's a lot of
talk about a meaningless season, but for
you, you look at it different as a
coach. I know where do you see the most
growth on a team even though this this
season hasn't been great? Well, I think
we we played a lot of young guys, you
know, and these guys have just gotten
better and better and so our future's
really bright that way that um every
player, you know, first, second, third
year player, I really feel like has made
huge strides this season as they've
gotten more reps and more opportunity.
And so, we have a lot of confidence in
those guys. And then, and then you blend
it with the veterans that we've got that
are playing at a high level. So, um I
feel really good about the direction of
this team and and you know, it's all we
can control is this week. We got Arizona
this week. We got to put our best foot
forward. Forget about what's going on
around us. Just focus on great game
plan, having a great week of practice,
winning the game, winning two games in a
row. The feeling we had in the locker
room, um responding with another way to
to win back-to-back games is is all we
can control right now.
>> Okay. You know, uh I know Jay Morrison
and his family are dealing with
something tough right now. Jay's, as you
all know, one of the greatest guys in
this business. So thoughts and prayers
with him and his family and and hate
that he's got to go for that, but I know
we're all here for him. So just want to
make sure he knows that and his family
knows that. Fantastic.
>> Thanks, Jack.